Finding local business leads one by one can eat hours.
You search maps, open listings, copy details, check websites,
and still end up with a messy spreadsheet.
AiFetchly's Local Business Finder turns that manual work
into an organized search.
Choose Google Maps for global coverage,
or Yandex Maps for Russia, CIS markets, and Turkey.
Open Local Business Finder from the left navigation.
In the Search tab, select your data source.
Enter the business type you want, like dentist,
Italian restaurant, plumber, or marketing agency.
Next, enter the target location.
You can use a city, address, zip code, or wider region.
Now tune the search. Set the maximum results from 1 to 50
and include website URLs for outreach-ready records.
Turn on reviews only when you need extra detail.
Show Browser is usually off unless you are debugging.
For Yandex searches, set language and region when needed.
You can also select an account and rotate proxies.
Click Start Search. AiFetchly runs in the background,
shows live progress, and lets you cancel if needed.
When the search finishes, the table gives you names,
ratings, reviews, addresses, phones, websites, and map links.
Copy everything as JSON, export CSV for spreadsheets,
or export JSON for downstream tools.
Local Business Finder gives you structured local leads,
ready for your next outreach step.